Emma just graduated from college and nervously entered the prestigious company.
She never expected to meet the legendary CEO Alex on her first day.
Alex looked at her coldly: 'So you're the new intern?'
Emma nodded nervously: 'Yes, Mr. Alex. I'm Emma.'
Alex frowned: 'I don't need decorations, only capable people.'
Emma gritted her teeth: 'I'll prove it to you!'
Thus began a workplace romance story...
Three months later, Emma won everyone's recognition with her outstanding performance.
Alex began to see this stubborn girl in a new light.
But an unexpected news broke the peace...
Emma discovered that Alex was her long-lost childhood friend!
Facing this shocking truth, how should they deal with it?